Battate Shoujo-tai: Idols Bringing Kyushu's Songs to the World
The girls' first performance in Indonesia
Many local audiences were captivated by their first performance in Indonesia.
This program is a documentary that closely follows the behind-the-scenes of their successful live performance.
Project Nukaten
The first live event in which the girls performed
Jakarta Japan Festival 2024
Japanese food and culture are popular in Indonesia
There were many live performances by artists and exhibits related to Japan.
and exhibits related to Japan.
Logging and the other members arrived there one day before the event
and will participate from the live rehearsal.
After arriving in Jakarta
they immediately attended the rehearsal on the day before the event.
The Batten Girls' Troupe was on a minute-by-minute schedule.
However, there was a problem right away.
The vehicle with microphones and sound equipment that they had brought from Japan for the concert
The vehicle carrying the microphones and sound equipment
got caught in a traffic jam
and would not arrive by the rehearsal time.
The girls were checking the flow on their phones
They had brought microphones
The rehearsal became a confirmation of standing position only without sound
Nervousness and anxiety were in the air as they were about to perform in Indonesia for the first time
In the end, we were unable to rehearse
We had to face this evening without being able to rehearse.
The song was over!
Good evening, Indonesian people!
Selemat Maalah!
Selemat Mahler.
Kami
Batten Girls Darling Japan
We are batten short time!
It's looking good.
Saya Kinan
Saya Miyu
Saya Riko
Saya Sakura
Saya Lino
Saya Ai
I love it!!!
I want to have fun today!
See you later.
I've already assigned roles now.
Here comes the trouble again.
While we were practicing our Indonesian MC.
The lights in the car went out
again.
An air of uneasiness began to hang in the air.
It was the Kaedeama of anxiety
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work
Good work, sir.
Good work, sir
Yes, pure paragi.
Perfect.
Many Indonesians who love Japan gathered at the venue.
Just before the show, the foodie Sakura Seta was having a munching time.
Eating potato chips sold in Indonesia.
He was ready to be in his usual condition.
This condition was gathered by many Indonesians who like Japanese people
something delicious.
Good morning.
Good luck and have a look!
please.
Bon appétit!
Sir?
Not exactly.
Here's a snack.
MARI BARCELA CELLA CELLA! I want to go!
There were numerous anxieties before the show, but the group from Japan took the lead, and the crowd was so enthusiastic that even the people of Indonesia joined in the calls.
The venue was united by the live performance of the Batten Girls' Corps.
NAKAYOSHI Did you know?
Men and Women Mochimei Sensei
woman woman woman woman woman woman woman woman woman woman woman woman woman woman woman woman woman woman woman woman woman woman woman woman woman woman woman
Ż is 우리가 good morning!
Thank you very much
Thank you for your hard work
This month we will be performing at the Aeon Mall in Jakarta in addition to the festival.
The members were looking forward to this live performance as a place to let the local people know about us.
We are going to perform live from now on. Second day
Aeon
It's so big!
Station
Station Night
Stations
Thank you for watching!
After a while, summer is crazy. Sandy beaches, parks
People passing each other, they all have love in their hearts.
Ghosts, ghosts, and giant power machines, trying their luck rather than trying out the ghosts
Dreamily, all the way to the balloon popping.
Project Batten
Nukeso gave the best live performance, but here another problem arose.
The director was troubled by the lack of quality shots.
The director was troubled.
Couldn't they take some more activity footage?
At that moment, a small amusement park on the top floor caught his eye.
The one in the back.
Is this it?
This one!
Wait a minute, this is bad.
This is bad, this is bad, this is bad.
This one!
Wait a minute. This is bad. This is bad.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Bike path!
It's a bike path!
But wait, this one, the one on the right.
If it's as bad as this, we might be able to make it.
But I'm gonna pull over.
I'll just pull over.
I can't reach my feet!
I can't reach my feet, Min-chan!
What's this?
Wait a minute, I'll try not to drop it!
Suddenly...
What's this?
Is it too steep?
Tell me, somebody!
Somebody help me!
Rap, rap, rap, rap.
I'm scared.
Ooh.
What's on the bike?
Uh...
It's going slower than I thought it would.
That's the first one!
So cute!
First car!
The first one!
That's great!
Oh, my God!
Here it comes!
They're here!
They're coming!
Thank you!
I can't do it! I can't!
The iron picture is gone.
Nukeso and the others moved on to the next venue, the Aeon Mall.
But the treraka mission continued.
This girl looks strong!
jouer
r mother's souvenir Schools
self
I
han
I han
This is a video handicap!
Video Handicap!
For the first time, Batten Shoujo-tai's live performance in Indonesia
Many local audiences gathered
and enjoyed the show regardless of age.
The girls' all-out performance and the enjoyment of their songs
transcended the language barrier and brought smiles to many faces.
We hope to bring smiles to the faces of people not only in Japan but also all over the world
and people around the world through music.
That is also a part of
music
may be one of their missions.
Project Manten
Thank you for the live concert.
Thank you very much.
We have received the video decision during the live performance.
Okay, let's go.
Yes, sir.
Oh!
I'll take care of it.
Paws up.
Next.
Wait, is that you, Mi-chan?
Last.
What's this?
Is that Mi-chan?
Yes!
Yes.